

HAO NGO

FRONT-END INTERN

PERSONAL INFORMATION

DOB: 15 Jan 2000

Gender: Male

Phone: 0944334052

Email: ngotrieuhao@gmail.com Address: District 8, Ho Chi Minh

City

Github: github.com/ngotrieuhao

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/h%E1%BA%A3o-

ng%C3%B4-795998184/

OBJECTIVE

Apply the knowledge learned in school and self-study about building a website to experience in a dynamic and professional environment. From there, develop professional skills, learn new programming knowledge to successfully complete the assigned work.

SKILLS

- Hard skill
 - HTML
 - CSS
 - Javascript

Soft skill

- Teamwork
- Self-Study
- Problem-Solving

EDUCATION

Major: Information Technology

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2021/06 - 2021/12

E-commerce Website (Shoes Store)

Role: Full-Stack Teamsize: 4 Responsibilities:

- Plan ideas and sketch out diagram
- Writing website code with programming languages such as HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Fixing any website issues or bugs that arise
- Turn UI/UX designs into prototypes, creating excellent interactions from designs
- Write functional requirement documents and guides

Skills: ASP.NET Core, C#, HTML, CSS, Javascript

2021/01 - 2021/04

Student Management Website

Role: Front-End Teamsize: 6 Responsibilities:

- Writing website code with programming languages such as HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Turn UI/UX designs into prototypes, creating

Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap

excellent interactions from designs

ACTIVITY

2019-2020 Join the Hackathon contest